[{"answer": " ... You've quite a sense of humor, Mr. Chance", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You live here?  ... We don't have any record of that", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " ... How long have you been living here", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Since you were a child", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yes, my friend, that is correct. Then he stopped visiting my garden", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You have me, I am here. What more proof do you need", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " I have no claim, my friend", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Correct", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yes sir. I'll report it right away", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Good day", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I've never ridden in an automobile", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " ... Yes. You can take me", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yes. He's a very careful driver", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "It's feeling better, but it's still very sore", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "May I ask your name", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Pardon me, was that Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " No. I'm a gardener", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No, Eve. I'm not related to Basil and my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Oh, fine", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " ... Straight out", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Claim...? ... Oh, claim, that's what my friend asked me", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "my friend, an attorney", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "my friend? Who's my friend", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "An attorney", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " ... You will join us for dinner, won't you, Mr. my friend", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "... So am I, my boy", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Do you need a secretary", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Oh. When you say 'Your house has been closed', you mean to say that your business was shut down", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yes, my friend. My leg is not very sore", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You're looking much better today, my friend", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Good morning, Mr. my friend, nice to see you again", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Fine, thank you.  We have an additional guest with us today, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Good morning, Mr. my friend", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Just fine, thank you, sir.  And you must be Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "It's so good to see you too, my friend, you look terrific", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You're right, Mr. President I don't like feeling sorry for myself", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You take care too, my friend", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " He's a decent fellow, the President, isn't he", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "He was quite impressed with your comments, my friend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " Hello, Eve", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Yes. It's feeling much better now", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I can't find Mr. my friend anywhere", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "What's he doing in the basement", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "He's in the basement", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I don't know, Mrs. my friend", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "my friend, the producer of 'This Evening' just called", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Of course. They would like you to appear on the show tonight. The Vice President was scheduled, but he had to cancel, and they asked if you would be interested", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Yes, I have seen that show on television", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Yes. I would like to be on that show", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "I like the President. He is a very nice man", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": " No, Eve. I like you to be here", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "And look who you brought with", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": " Oh, I've been just dying to meet you, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "my friend, this is my friend..", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "my friend, this is Mrs. my friend", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": " So you know your my friend in Russian, do you? Mr. my friend, I must confess I had suspected as much all along", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Yes, it is very good", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Well, if that's what you want, then I want it too.  We can go this way", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Tell Eve? You mean Mrs. Rand", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Gentlemen, I didn't call you here at such an hour to make accusations, I just want to explore the possibilities. Now, I have three question", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Very well... Can we rule out inefficiency...", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": " I don't think that's entirely true, my friend", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Well, Mr. President... They don't quite know what to think", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "I just don't excite you at all... I don't know what you want... I don't know what you like..", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": " To watch...? To watch me...", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "I like to watch", "docId": "Being-There.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Yes. I like to watch", "qsentId": 68}]